<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link href="http://arxiv.org/api/query?search_query%3Dall%3Askyrmion%26id_list%3D%26start%3D0%26max_results%3D10" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <title type="html">ArXiv Query: search_query=all:skyrmion&amp;id_list=&amp;start=0&amp;max_results=10</title>
  <id>http://arxiv.org/api/geeNEGlNK8iPWHU/uGlce+Cy29A</id>
  <updated>2016-10-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
  <opensearch:totalResults xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/">1335</opensearch:totalResults>
  <opensearch:startIndex xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/">0</opensearch:startIndex>
  <opensearch:itemsPerPage xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/">10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1005.2488v4</id>
    <updated>2011-03-29T12:35:45Z</updated>
    <published>2010-05-14T09:48:42Z</published>
    <title>Non-existence of Skyrmion-Skyrmion and Skyrmion-anti-Skyrmion static
  equilibria</title>
    <summary>  We consider classical static Skyrmion-anti-Skyrmion and Skyrmion-Skyrmion
configurations, symmetric with respect to a reflection plane, or symmetric up
to a $G$-parity transformation respectively. We show that the stress tensor
component completely normal to the reflection plane, and hence its integral
over the plane, is negative definite or positive definite respectively.
Classical Skyrmions always repel classical Skyrmions and classical Skyrmions
always attract classical anti-Skyrmions and thus no static equilibrium, whether
stable or unstable, is possible in either case. No other symmetry assumption is
made and so our results also apply to multi-Skyrmion configurations. Our
results are consistent with existing analyses of Skyrmion forces at large
separation, and with numerical results on Skymion-anti-Skyrmion configurations
in the literature which admit a different reflection symmetry. They also hold
for the massive Skyrme model. We also point out that reflection symmetric
self-gravitating Skyrmions or black holes with Skyrmion hair cannot rest in
symmetric equilibrium with self-gravitating anti-Skyrmions.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>G. W. Gibbons</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>C. M. Warnick</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>W. W. Wong</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1063/1.3523469</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1063/1.3523469" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">v2 Typos corrected, refs added. v3 Journal version</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">J. Math. Phys. 52:012905,2011</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1005.2488v4" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1005.2488v4" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="hep-th" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="hep-th" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="math-ph" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="math.MP" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.7283v10</id>
    <updated>2015-01-13T01:47:19Z</updated>
    <published>2014-03-28T06:12:19Z</published>
    <title>Skyrmion-skyrmion and skyrmion-edge repulsions in skyrmion-based
  racetrack memory</title>
    <summary>  Magnetic skyrmions are promising for building next-generation magnetic
memories and spintronic devices due to their stability, small size and the
extremely low currents needed to move them. In particular, skyrmion-based
racetrack memory is attractive for information technology, where skyrmions are
used to store information as data bits instead of traditional domain walls.
Here we numerically demonstrate the impacts of skyrmion-skyrmion and
skyrmion-edge repulsions on the feasibility of skyrmion-based racetrack memory.
The reliable and practicable spacing between consecutive skyrmionic bits on the
racetrack as well as the ability to adjust it are investigated. Clogging of
skyrmionic bits is found at the end of the racetrack, leading to the reduction
of skyrmion size. Further, we demonstrate an effective and simple method to
avoid the clogging of skyrmionic bits, which ensures the elimination of
skyrmionic bits beyond the reading element. Our results give guidance for the
design and development of future skyrmion-based racetrack memory.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Xichao Zhang</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>G. P. Zhao</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Hans Fangohr</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>J. Ping Liu</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>W. X. Xia</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>J. Xia</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>F. J. Morvan</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1038/srep07643</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1038/srep07643" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">15 pages, 6 figures</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">Sci. Rep. 5, 7643</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.7283v10" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1403.7283v10" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.mtrl-sci" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mtrl-sci" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1412.0772v2</id>
    <updated>2015-02-13T14:06:16Z</updated>
    <published>2014-12-02T03:28:17Z</published>
    <title>Charged skyrmions on the surface of a topological insulator</title>
    <summary>  We consider the interplay between magnetic skyrmions in an insulating thin
film and the Dirac surface states of a 3D topological insulator (TI), coupled
by proximity effect. The magnetic texture of skyrmions can lead to confinement
of Dirac states at the skyrmion radius, where out of plane magnetization
vanishes. This confinement can result in charging of the skyrmion texture. The
presence of bound states is robust in an external magnetic field, which is
needed to stabilize skyrmions. It is expected that for relevant experimental
parameters skyrmions will have a few bound states that can be tuned using an
external magnetic field. We argue that these charged skyrmions can be
manipulated directly by an electric field, with skyrmion mobility proportional
to the number of bound states at the skyrmion radius. Coupling skyrmionic thin
films to a TI surface can provide a more direct and efficient way of
controlling skyrmion motion in insulating materials. This provides a new
dimension in the study of skyrmion manipulation.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Hilary M. Hurst</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Dmitry K. Efimkin</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Jiadong Zang</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Victor Galitski</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1103/PhysRevB.91.060401</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1103/PhysRevB.91.060401" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">additional references, minor corrections</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">Physical Review B 91, 060401 (2015)</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1412.0772v2" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1412.0772v2" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/0906.5583v2</id>
    <updated>2009-12-01T15:08:07Z</updated>
    <published>2009-06-30T14:21:33Z</published>
    <title>Skyrmion--Anti-Skyrmion Chains</title>
    <summary>  Static axially symmetric sphaleron-type solutions describing chains of
interpolating Skyrmion--anti-Skyrmions have been constructed numerically. The
configurations are characterized by two integers n and m, where $\pm n$ are the
winding numbers of the constituent Skyrmion and anti-Skyrmion and the second
integer m defines type of the solution, it has zero topological charge for even
m and for odd values of m the Skyrmion--anti-Skyrmion chain has topological
charge n. For the vanishing mass term we confirm the existence of such chain
solutions for winding number $|n| \ge 2$. The similarity with
monopole--anti-monopole pairs is highlighted.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Ya. Shnir</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>D. H. Tchrakian</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1088/1751-8113/43/2/025401</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1088/1751-8113/43/2/025401" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10 pages, 4 figures, typos corrected, Table 2 added</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">J.Phys.A43:025401,2010</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/0906.5583v2" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/0906.5583v2" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="hep-th" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="hep-th" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1405.1568v3</id>
    <updated>2014-09-24T13:56:22Z</updated>
    <published>2014-05-07T10:53:35Z</published>
    <title>Magnon-skyrmion scattering in chiral magnets</title>
    <summary>  Chiral magnets support topological skyrmion textures due to the
Dzyaloshinskii-Moriya spin-orbit interaction. In the presence of a sufficiently
large applied magnetic field, such skyrmions are large amplitude excitations of
the field-polarized magnetic state. We investigate analytically the interaction
between such a skyrmion excitation and its small amplitude fluctuations, i.e.,
the magnons in a clean two-dimensional chiral magnet. The magnon spectrum is
found to include two magnon-skyrmion bound states corresponding to a breathing
mode and, for intermediate fields, a quadrupolar mode, which will give rise to
subgap magnetic and electric resonances. Due to the skyrmion topology, the
magnons scatter from a Aharonov-Bohm flux density that leads to skew and
rainbow scattering, characterized by an asymmetric differential cross section
with, in general, multiple peaks. As a consequence of the skew scattering, a
finite density of skyrmions will generate a topological magnon Hall effect.
Using the conservation law for the energy-momentum tensor, we demonstrate that
the magnons also transfer momentum to the skyrmion. As a consequence, a magnon
current leads to magnon pressure reflected in a momentum-transfer force in the
Thiele equation of motion for the skyrmion. This force is reactive and governed
by the scattering cross sections of the skyrmion; it causes not only a finite
skyrmion velocity but also a large skyrmion Hall effect. Our results provide,
in particular, the basis for a theory of skyrmion caloritronics for a dilute
skyrmion gas in clean insulating chiral magnets.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Christoph Schütte</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Markus Garst</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1103/PhysRevB.90.094423</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1103/PhysRevB.90.094423" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">19 pages, 13 figures; (v2) typos corrected; (v3) clarifications
  added; extended discussion of the local skyrmion instability as well as of
  the skyrmion Hall angle</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">Phys. Rev. B 90, 094423 (2014)</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1405.1568v3" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1405.1568v3" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/0908.3385v1</id>
    <updated>2009-08-24T08:34:50Z</updated>
    <published>2009-08-24T08:34:50Z</published>
    <title>Half-Skyrmion theory for high-temperature superconductivity</title>
    <summary>  We review the half-Skyrmion theory for copper-oxide high-temperature
superconductivity. In the theory, doped holes create a half-Skyrmion spin
texture which is characterized by a topological charge. The formation of the
half-Skyrmion is described in the single hole doped system, and then the
half-Skyrmion excitation spectrum is compared with the angle-resolved
photoemission spectroscopy results in the undoped system. Multi-half-Skyrmion
configurations are studied by numerical simulations. We show that
half-Skyrmions carry non-vanishing topological charge density below a critical
hole doping concentration \sim 30% even in the absence of antiferromagnetic
long-range order. The magnetic structure factor exhibits incommensurate peaks
in stripe ordered configurations of half-Skyrmions and anti-half-Skyrmions. The
interaction mediated by half-Skyrmions leads to d_{x^2-y^2}-wave
superconductivity. We also describe pseudogap behavior arising from the
excitation spectrum of a composite particle of a half-Skyrmion and doped hole.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Takao Morinari</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">To appear in "The Multifaceted Skyrmion" (World Scientific) ed. G.E.
  Brown and M. Rho; 21 pages, 7 figures</arxiv:comment>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/0908.3385v1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/0908.3385v1" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.supr-con" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.supr-con" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.6283v1</id>
    <updated>2013-11-25T13:02:04Z</updated>
    <published>2013-11-25T13:02:04Z</published>
    <title>Target-skyrmions and skyrmion clusters in nanowires of chiral magnets</title>
    <summary>  In bulk non-centrosymmetric magnets the chiral Dzyaloshinskii-Moriya exchange
stabilizes tubular skyrmions with a reversed magnetization in their centers.
While the double-twist is favorable in the center of a skyrmion, it gives rise
to an excess of the energy density at the outskirt. Therefore, magnetic
anisotropies are required to make skyrmions more favorable than the conical
spiral state in bulk materials. Using Monte Carlo simulations, we show that in
magnetic nanowires unusual skyrmions with a doubly twisted core and a number of
concentric helicoidal undulations (target-skyrmions) are thermodynamically
stable even in absence of single-ion anisotropies. Such skyrmions are free of
magnetic charges and, since the angle describing the direction of magnetization
at the surface depends on the radius of the nanowire and an applied magnetic
field, they carry a non-integer skyrmion charge s &gt; 1. This state competes with
clusters of spatially separated s=1 skyrmions. For very small radii, the
target-skyrmion transforms into a skyrmion with s &lt; 1, that resembles the
vortex-like state stabilized by surface-induced anisotropies.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>A. O. Leonov</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>U. K. Rößler</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>M. Mostovoy</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1051/epjconf/20147505002</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1051/epjconf/20147505002" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">EPJ Web of Conferences 75, 05002 (2014)</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.6283v1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1311.6283v1" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.3350v1</id>
    <updated>2014-04-13T07:00:46Z</updated>
    <published>2014-04-13T07:00:46Z</published>
    <title>A reversible conversion between a skyrmion and a domain-wall pair in
  junction geometry</title>
    <summary>  A skyrmion is a topological texture in the continuum field theory. Recent
experimental observation of skyrmions in chiral magnet evokes a flourish of its
extensive study. Skyrmion is expected to be a key component of the next
generation spintronics device called skyrmionics. On the other hand, there is a
well established memory device encoded by a sequence of domain walls. A
skyrmion carries a topological number, whereas a domain wall does not.
Nevertheless, we show a conversion is possible between a skyrmion and a
domain-wall pair by connecting wide and narrow nanowires, enabling the
information transmission between skyrmion device and domain-wall device. Our
results will be the basis of a hybrid device made of skyrmions and domain
walls, where the encoded information in domain walls is converted into
skyrmions, and then read out by converting the skyrmions back to domain walls
after a functional control of the skyrmions.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Yan Zhou</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Motohiko Ezawa</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1038/ncomms5652</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1038/ncomms5652" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">8 pages, 5 figures</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">Nature Communications 5, 4652 (2014)</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.3350v1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1404.3350v1" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mtrl-sci" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/1512.05012v1</id>
    <updated>2015-12-15T23:44:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-12-15T23:44:03Z</published>
    <title>Ginzburg-Landau theory for skyrmions in inversion-symmetric magnets with
  competing interactions</title>
    <summary>  Magnetic skyrmions have attracted considerable attention recently for their
huge potential in spintronic applications. Generally skyrmions are big compared
to the atomic lattice constant, which allows for the Ginzburg-Landau type
description in the continuum limit. Such a description successfully captures
the main experimental observations on skyrmions in B20 compound without
inversion symmetry. Skyrmions can also exist in inversion-symmetric magnets
with competing interactions. Here we derive a general Ginzburg-Landau theory
for skyrmions in these magnets valid in the long wavelength limit. We study the
unusual static and dynamical properties of skyrmions based on the derived
Ginzburg-Landau theory. We show that an easy axis spin anisotropy is sufficient
to stabilize a skyrmion lattice. Interestingly, the skyrmion in
inversion-symmetric magnets has a new internal degree of freedom associated
with the rotation of helicity, i.e. the "spin" of the skyrmion as a particle,
in addition to the usual translational motion of skyrmions (orbital motion).
The orbital and spin degree of freedoms of an individual skyrmion can couple to
each other, and give rise to unusual behavior that is absent for the skyrmions
stabilized by the Dzyaloshinskii-Moriya interaction. The derived
Ginzburg-Landau theory provides a convenient and general framework to discuss
skyrmion physics and will facilitate the search for skyrmions in
inversion-symmetric magnets.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>Shi-Zeng Lin</name>
    </author>
    <author>
      <name>Satoru Hayami</name>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1103/PhysRevB.93.064430</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1103/PhysRevB.93.064430" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">15 pages and 13 figures</arxiv:comment>
    <arxiv:journal_ref xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">Phys. Rev. B 93, 064430 (2016)</arxiv:journal_ref>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1512.05012v1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1512.05012v1" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.mes-hall" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.soft" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat.str-el" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="nlin.PS" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://arxiv.org/abs/cond-mat/0002053v1</id>
    <updated>2000-02-03T12:11:01Z</updated>
    <published>2000-02-03T12:11:01Z</published>
    <title>Quantum Critical Dynamics of the Skyrmion Lattice</title>
    <summary>  Near to filling fraction $\nu=1$, the quantum Hall ferromagnet contains
multiple Skyrmion spin excitations. This multi-Skyrmion system has a
tremendously rich quantum-critical structure. This is simplified when Skyrmions
are pinned by disorder. We calculate the nuclear relaxation rate in this case
and compare the result with experiment. We discus how such measurements may be
used to further probe the quantum-critical structure of the multi-Skyrmion
system.
</summary>
    <author>
      <name>A. G. Green</name>
      <arxiv:affiliation xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">U. of Cambridge</arxiv:affiliation>
    </author>
    <arxiv:doi xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">10.1103/PhysRevB.61.R16299</arxiv:doi>
    <link title="doi" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1103/PhysRevB.61.R16299" rel="related"/>
    <arxiv:comment xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom">9 pages, 3 figures</arxiv:comment>
    <link href="http://arxiv.org/abs/cond-mat/0002053v1" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link title="pdf" href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/cond-mat/0002053v1" rel="related" type="application/pdf"/>
    <arxiv:primary_category xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" term="cond-mat" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
    <category term="cond-mat" scheme="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom"/>
  </entry>
</feed>
